A Guide to the Richmond Jaycees, 1936-2002
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Richmond Jaycees, 1936-2002
The Library of Virginia
37705
63.45 cu. ft.
Richmond Jaycees
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Privacy protected and confidential information is restricted from public access for 75 years. Restricted records in this collection have been sealed but not removed from the collection.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Richmond Jaycees
Historical Information
The Richmond Jaycees were founded on May 15, 1936 by a group of fifty men who came together as charters members. The organization was originally known as the Richmond Junior Board o Trade. The group was incorporated September 3, 1940.
Scope and Content
Records, 1936-2002, of the Richmond Jaycees, a volunteer, civic based organization located in Richmond, Virginia. The records include administrative files, correspondence, newsletters, project files and photographs. Of interest are the project files that detail the Richmond Jaycees extensive charity work including such projects as the Special Olympic and Little Santa Christmas Party for underprivileged children, and public outreach programs such as helping the elderly and get out the vote campaigns. As well as community related projects such as the Richmond Christmas Parade and fundraising projects such as an annual Christmas tree sale.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Administrative Files
Newsletters
Project Files
Photographs
Miscellaneous
Contents List
- Administration Files, 1939-2002.
  This series consists of files related to the day to day running of the Richmond Jaycees, including minutes of board meetings, United States Jaycee handbooks and procedures, and the correspondence of several Richmond Jaycees presidents.
  The series is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
  - Agenda -- Board of Directors Meetings, 1978-1979. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agenda -- Board of Directors Meetings, 1989-1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agenda -- Board of Directors Meeting, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agenda -- Board of Directors Meetings, 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agenda -- Executive Committee Meetings, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agenda -- Executive Committee Meetings, 1991-1992. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Annual Awards and Installation Banquet Program, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting Program, 1974. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Articles of Incorporation, not dated. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Associate Membership Applications (CLOSED UNTIL 2059), 1939-1984. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Audited Financial Statement, 1962. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Awards Committee, 1984-1988. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Balance Sheet, 1964. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bosses Night Programs, 1954-1976. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bosses Night Invites, 1989-1992. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Budget, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - By-laws, 1988-1989. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - By-laws, 1994. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - By-laws, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Calendar of Events, 2001. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Chairman's Planning Guide example, 2000. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Chairman's Planning Guide Manual, 1995-1996. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee Reports, 1952-1953. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Community Development, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contracts, 1990-1992. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence -- Miscellaneous, 1994-1995. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence -- Orientation/Open House, 2001. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dinner Meetings, 1990-1991. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Distinguished Service Award Presentation Programs, 1945-1970. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Enrollment and Growth, not dated. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Executive Cabinet, 1975. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1987. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1991. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Federal Tax Return, 1992. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Federated Arts Council of Richmond, Inc., 1981-1982. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Financial Management Pinnacle Area, 2000. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Financial Report to Our Sustaining Members, 1972-1975. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - First Ladies Handbook, 1982-1983. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Forms, 1982-1983. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - General Ledger, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Gift from Fuji, Japan Jaycee President, ca. 1964. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Certificates of Recognition, 1977-1986. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Inactive Members A-G (CLOSED UNTIL 2067), 1992. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Inactive Members H-M (CLOSED UNTIL 2067), 1992. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Inactive Members N-R (CLOSED UNTIL 2067), 1992. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Inactive Members S-Z (CLOSED UNTIL 2067), 1992. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Individual Development, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Installation and Awards Night Programs, 1972-1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Insurance, 1984-1996. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - International Free Enterprise Day Proclamation, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Jaycees History Committee, 1948-1979. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Jaycee Week Proclamation, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Junior Chamber International Publications and Materials, 1998. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Keyman Luncheon, 2000. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Key Man Club Card File, 1956-1984. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Key Man Club, 1958-1979. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Key Man Club, 1978-1989. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Key Man Club, 1990-1991. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "A" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1980-1989. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "B" (CLOSED UNTIL 2050), 1940-1975. (Box 12a, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "B" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1978-1989. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "C" (CLOSED UNTIL 2049), 1940-1974. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "C" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1974-1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "D" (CLOSED UNTIL 2055), 1976-1980. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "E" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1971-1989. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "F" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1977-1989. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "G" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1938-1990. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "H-He" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1978-1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Hi-Ho" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1940-1990. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Hu-Hy" (CLOSED UNTIL 2063), 1942-1988. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "I" (CLOSED UNTIL 2062), 1938-1987. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "J-K" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1976-1990. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "L" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1982-1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "M" (CLOSED UNTIL 2050), 1938-1975. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Membership Directory, 1972-1973. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Mc" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1939-1989. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "N-O" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1974-1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "P-Q" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1977-1990. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "R" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1983-1990. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "S-Sm" (CLOSED UNTIL 2048), 1938-1973. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "S-Sm" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1979-1990. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Sn-Sr" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1942-1989. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "St-Sy" (CLOSED UNTIL 2050), 1936-1975. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "St-Sy" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1982-1990. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "T-Th" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1938-1990. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Ti-Ty" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1938-1989. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "U-V" (CLOSED UNTIL 2064), 1938-1989. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Wa" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1940-1990. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "We-Wh" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1940-1990. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Wi-Wy" (CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1940-1990. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Membership Applications and Activities Record "Y-Z" (CLOSED UNTIL 2063), 1985-1988. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications(CLOSED UNTIL 2066), 1990-1991. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Membership Applications(CLOSED UNTIL 2071), 1991-1996. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Membership Applications(CLOSED UNTIL 2068), 1993. (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Membership Applications(CLOSED UNTIL 2070), 1995. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Membership Directory, 1983. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Membership Handbook, 1978-1979. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Membership Handbook, 1981-1982. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Membership Handbook, 1984-1985. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Membership Handbook, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Membership Handbook, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Membership Recruitment and Retention Third Quarter Review, ca. 1994. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Membership Roster, 1970. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Membership Roster, 1971. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Membership Roster, 1972. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Membership Roster, 1974-1975. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Membership Roster, 1975-1976. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Membership Roster, 1977-1978. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Membership Roster, 1979-1980. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Membership Roster, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Membership Roster, 1987. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Membership Roster, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Membership Roster, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Membership Roster, 1996. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Membership Roster (CLOSED UNTIL 2076), 2001. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Membership Roster (CLOSED UNTIL 2077), 2001-2002. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Metro Richmond Chamber of Commerce, 1977-1978. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1976-1978. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1978. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1978-1979. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee, 1980-1981. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1981-1982. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1982-1983. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1983-1984. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1984-1985. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1989-1990. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1990-1991. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors and Executive Committee Meetings, 1991-1992. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Minutes -- Board of Directors, 2001-2002. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Minutes -- Monthly Meeting, 1976-1978. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Minutes -- Monthly Meetings, 1978-1980. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1936-1988. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - New Member Handbook, ca. 2001. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Nomination for Sidney D. Peck Memorial Award for Outstanding Local President, 1963-1964. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Officers Training, 1985. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Officer Training, 1988-1996. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Officer Roster, 1996-1997. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Officer Training, 2001. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Official Election Ballots, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Orientation, 1990-1991. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Outstanding Young Citizen, 1988-1989. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Outstanding Young Man Award Programs, 1958-1984. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Past Presidents, 1977-1983. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Past Presidents' Night Program, not dated. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Personal Property, 1963-1980. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Records, 1973-1978. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Policy and Procedure Manual, 1964. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1965. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1966. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1968. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1970. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual, 1975. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Policy and Procedures Manual Amendments, 1976-1984. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Presidents File -- Jimmie G. Anderson, 1981-1982. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Presidents File -- Robert M. Kelly Jr., 1984-1985. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Presidents File -- Channing J. Martin, 1985-1986. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Presidents File -- Randy Shelton, 1986-1987. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Presidents File -- Bobbi Arduini, 1987-1988. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Presidents File -- Charlie Diederich, 1988-1989. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Presidents File -- Frances E. Daniel, 1990-1991. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Presidents File -- J. Melleky,. (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Presidents File -- Doug Robelen, 1993-1994. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Press Night Program, 1976. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Project Planning Guide, not dated. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Report on Examination of Accounts and Records of Administration, 1964. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Report on Examination of Cash Receipts and Disbursements, 1950. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Report on Examination of Financial Statements, 1975. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Report on Proceeds from the Richmond 88 Convention Corporation, 1990.
  - Report on Richmond Jaycees, 1970-1971. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Report on the Examination of Accounts and Records of Administration, 1966. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Report on Year End Examination, 1954. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Richmond Jaycees 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1986. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Richmond Jaycee History, 1962-1970. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Richmond Jaycees -- Miscellaneous Brochures, 1958-1959. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Richmond Jaycees 25th Anniversary Celebration, 1962. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Secretary's Annual Report, 1967-1968. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - State Corporation Commission, 1967-1989. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Statement of Income, 1990-1991. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Suggested Changes for Election Procedures, ca. 2001. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1987. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Sustaining Membership, 1988. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Sustaining Membership Certificates, not dated. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Report, 1983. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - United States Jaycees, 1977-1980. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - United States Jaycees Chapter President's Handbook, 1985-1986. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - United States Jaycees Chapter President's Handbook, not dated. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - United States Jaycees Chapter President's Management Handbook, 1978-1979. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - United States Jaycees 50th Anniversary Booklet, 1970. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - United States Jaycees Membership(CLOSED UNTIL 2065), 1989-1990. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - United States Jaycees Membership(CLOSED UNTIL 2066), 1990-1991. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1970-1971. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1971-1972. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1975-1976. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1979-1980. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1980-1981. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - United States Jaycees Officers and Directors Guide, 1982-1983. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - United States Jaycees Publications, 1972. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Jaycees Awards Presented to Richmond Jaycees, 2000. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Jaycees Handbook, 1975-1976. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Jaycees Public Relations Programming Manual, not dated. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Jaycees Public Relations and Communications Tool Kit, 2001. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Jaycees Resource Guide, 1997-1998. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Virginia Jaycees State Convention Programs, 1960-1971. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Year End Report, 1989-1990. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Year End Report, 1990-1991. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Year End Report, 1992-1993. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Young Men Can Change the World: The Jaycee Story, 1971. (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Newsletters, 1943-2005.
  This series consists of newsletters created by the Richmond Jaycees to supply meeting and activities information to its membership. The newsletters have had several titles over the years. It first appeared as "As Jaycees See," then became "The Jaycees News Letter," before finally changing its name to "Jaybill."
  - As Jaycees See, 1943-1944. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1944-1945. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1946. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1946-1947. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1947-1948. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1948-1949. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1949-1950. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1950-1952. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1952-1953. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1953-1954. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1954-1955. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1955-1956. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1956-1957. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1957-1958. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1958-1959. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1959-1960. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1960-1961. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1961-1962. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1962-1963. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1963-1964. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1964-1965. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1965-1966. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - The Jaycee News Letter, 1966-1967. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Jaybill, 1968-1969. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Jaybill, 1969-1970. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Jaybill, 1970-1971. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Jaybill, 1971-1972. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Jaybill, 1972-1973. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Jaybill, 1973-1974. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Jaybill, 1974-1975. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Jaybill, 1975-1976. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Jaybill, 1976-1977. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Jaybill, 1977-1978. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jaybill, 1978-1979. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jaybill, 1979-1980. (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Jaybill, 1981. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Jaybill, 1982-1983. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Jaybill, 1983. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Jaybill, 1984. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Jaybill, 1985. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Jaybill, 1985-1986. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Jaybill, 1986-1987. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jaybill, 1987-1988. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jaybill, 1988-1989. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Jaybill, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Jaybill, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jaybill, 1994-1995. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jaybill, 1995-1996. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jaybill, 1996-1997. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jaybill, 2001. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Jaybill, 2002. (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Jaybill, 2003-2005. (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Project Files, 1956-2002.
  This series consists of files created for the various projects conducted by the Richmond Jaycees. These projects range from the planning of meeting related to Jaycee membership to charity events, fundraising activities and community outreach. The Project files include descriptions of the project, budget, time line for implementation of the project, correspondence related to the project and often photographs taken during the project.
  - A Day in the Park, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - A Day in the Park, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Ad Supplement, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Adopt a Grandparent, 2002. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Adopt A Highway, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Adopt A Highway, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Adopt A Highway, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Adopt A Highway, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Adopt A Highway, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Aid to Disadvantaged Businesses, 1970-1971. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Aid to the Blind, 1976. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Aid to the Blind, 1977-1978. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Aid to the Blind, 1978-1979. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Aid to the Blind, 1982. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - AIDS Awareness, 1992. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "Ain't Scared" Sports Series, 1993-1994. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - All American City Entry, 1966-1967. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - American Council for the Blind Convention, 1990. (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - American Freedom Train, 1976. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - American History Awards, 1961-1962. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - American History Awards, 1963. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - American History Awards, 1964-1965. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - American History Awards, 1966. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - American History Awards, 1968. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Annual Billing, 1992-1993. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Annual Forum -- Abortion, 1975. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Annual Forum -- Proposed Revision to the Virginia Constitution, 1969. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Anti Drop Out Prevention Team, 1966-1967. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Antique Auto Club Parking, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Apple Butter Sunday, 1972. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Apple Jelly Sunday, 1969. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Apple Jelly Sunday, 1970. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Apple Jelly Sunday, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Arrangement Committee Activities, 1967-1968. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Arrest Amblyopia, 1969. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Art Appreciation, 1990. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Art of Massage Seminar, 1987. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Art of Massage Seminar, 1989. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Audit, 1992-1993. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Awards, 1991-1992. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Awards, 1991-1992. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Awards, 1992-1993. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Awards Committee, 1975-1976. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Awards Committee, 1976-1977. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Azalea Affiliation, 1990-1991. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Bartending Basics, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Basic Car Maintenance, 1989. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1986-1987. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1986-1987. (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1987. (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1991. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Beach Music Festival, 1992-1993. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Beach Music Festival Membership Booth, ca. 1991-1992. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Bicentennial Week Poster Distribution, 1976. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Bicycle Safety, 1961. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Bid to Host Mid-Atlantic/Northeast Metro Regional Workshop, 1975-1976. (Box 28, Folder 6-7)
  - Bid for State Functions, 1964. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Bid to Host State Meetings, 1964-1965. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Bingo, 1976-1977. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1987. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1987. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Board Orientation, 1987. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Bowl for Breath Tournament, 1988. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bowling for Fun, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Boy Scout Show Judges, 1984. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Show Judges, 1985. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout -- Together We Organize Dinner, 1971. (Box 29, Folder 6)